Creating courses that truly engage
students is hard. Static slides and long
videos just don't cut it anymore. That's
why educators are switching to Encrypt,
the AI-powered tool that turns boring
slides into interactive avatar-guided
lessons. Here's why they love it. With
Encrypt, your slides come alive.
Students can click on any section, a
diagram, a formula, or a key point,
and instantly hear a friendly avatar
explain it in detail. This interactivity
keeps learners hooked, boosting course
completion rates by up to 60%.
Say goodbye to endless scripting and
editing. With Ancrypt, you just speak
naturally, and our AI turns your voice
notes into polished scripts. Add
lifelike avatars in minutes, saving you
10+ hours every month. You can reach
students everywhere, no matter their
language. Ancrypt auto-translates your
explanations into 20+ languages,
So your courses can go global without
extra effort. Ancrypt isn't just a tool,
it's a game changer for course creators.
Ready to make your courses unforgettable?
Try Ancrypt today.