With Ancript, turning your slides into an
interactive experience is effortless.
Here's how it works. You start by
simply importing your PowerPoint or PDF.
Our system seamlessly processes it,
allowing you to view and interact with
your slides right within our platform. No
formatting issues, no hassle, just your
content, ready to enhance.
Next, you decide where you want to add
explanations. Just click on any
section of your slides that needs more
clarity,and you're ready to go.
Now, instead of spending hours perfecting
a script, you can simply speak your
thoughts naturally, just like you would
when explaining to a friend. No pressure,
no need for perfection. Our AI then
takes over, refining your unstructured
thoughts into a clear, polished script.
From there, a lifelike avatar, complete
with expressive speech and natural
gestures, delivers your explanation.
making your content more engaging and
easier to understand. Once you're happy
with the explanations, sharing is just as
simple. With a single link, you can send
your interactive presentation to anyone,
allowing your audience to explore the
slides while engaging with the AI-powered
explanations at their own pace. With
AnCrypt, presentations are no longer just
static documents. They become immersive,
AI-driven experiences that captivate and
educate effortlessly.